<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on </title>
    <link>https://www.wojciechmazurek.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.wojciechmazurek.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>National Cyber League </title>
      <link>https://www.wojciechmazurek.com/projects/ncl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.wojciechmazurek.com/projects/ncl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Spring 2022 -&#xA;Participated in the NCL competition which included practice scenarios that focused on the following: Open-source intelligence, Cryptography, Password cracking, Log analysis, Network Traffic Analysis, Data forensics, Scanning and reconnaissance, Web app exploitation, and Enumeration and exploitation; Scored top 10% in the nation, top scorer in my classes&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University Rover Challenge-Capstone Project</title>
      <link>https://www.wojciechmazurek.com/projects/urc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.wojciechmazurek.com/projects/urc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AUG 2020 – DEC 2020 - Worked in groups using programs such as SolidWorks to create 3D printed parts; Conducted research to develop the best ways of testing soil samples&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App for CargoShot Inc.</title>
      <link>https://www.wojciechmazurek.com/projects/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.wojciechmazurek.com/projects/app/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OCT 2022 – FEB 2023 - This project involved processing visual data using machine learning models to detect specific classes of warehouse pallet objects. A prototype computer vision system app was developed using Roboflow, using AI to enhance object detection capabilities in a warehouse environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Longitudinal Study of Factors that Affect User Interactions with Social Media and Email Spam </title>
      <link>https://www.wojciechmazurek.com/projects/thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.wojciechmazurek.com/projects/thesis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Conducted a comprehensive study involving 221 participants to analyze factors influencing user interactions with spam; Designed and administered an online survey to collect demographic information, education background, spam training, and interaction experiences; Performed longitudinal analysis and logistic regression to identify key factors reducing the likelihood of spam victimization; Found that individuals with higher education levels and a STEM background were significantly less likely to interact with or fall victim to spam.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
